[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What does the idiom ^don't judge a book by its cover ^mean?",
        "options": {
          "A": "Books should have beautiful covers",
          "B": " You shouldn't judge people based on appearance.",
          "C": "Everyone should read more books.",
          "D": "A book’s title tells everything about it."
        },
        "correct_option": " You shouldn't judge people based on appearance."
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": " What is the synonym of \"purchase?",
        "options":{
          "A": "Sell",
          "B": "Buy",
          "C": "Give",
          "D": "Exchange"
        },
        "correct_option": "Buy"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What does \"Hijab\" refer to?",
        "options":{
          "A": " A type of dress",
          "B": "A head covering worn by some Muslim women",
          "C": "A traditional meal",
          "D": "A hairstyle"
        },
        "correct_option": "A head covering worn by some Muslim women"
    },
  {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "\"Rolling in money\" means:",
        "options":{
          "A": "Being extremely poor",
          "B": "Having a lot of money",
          "C": "Losing all your money",
          "D": "Investing wisely"
        },

        "correct_option": "Having a lot of money"
    },
  {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which of the following is a positive adjective for a job?",
        "options":{
          "A": "Boring",
          "B": "Depressing",
          "C": "Rewarding",
          "D": "Exhausting"
        },
        "correct_option": "Rewarding"
    },
  {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is the opposite of \"stressful\"?",
        "options":{
          "A": "Relaxing",
          "B": "Demanding",
          "C": "Challenging",
          "D": "Motivating"
        },
        "correct_option": "Relaxing"
    },
  {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "If you \"keep mum\", you are:?",
        "options":{
          "A": "Telling a secret",
          "B": "Staying silent",
          "C": "Speaking loudly",
          "D": "Asking for help"
        },
        "correct_option": "Staying silent"
    },
  {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "\"To each their own\" means:?",
        "options": {
          "A": "Everyone has their own preferences",
          "B": "You must follow the rules.",
          "C": "People should be the same",
          "D": "It is important to share"
        },
        "correct_option": "Everyone has their own preferences"
    },
  {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What does \"chop chop\" mean?",
        "options": {
          "A": "Hurry up!",
          "B": "Take it easy",
          "C": "Stop talking",
          "D": "Cook something"
        },
        "correct_option": "Hurry up!"
    },
  {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which one is a synonym of \"extremely tired\"?",
        "options":  {
          "A": "I’m beat.",
          "B": "I’m starving.",
          "C": "I’m excited",
          "D": "I’m furious"
        },
        "correct_option": "I’m beat."
    }
]